Now I have shown you all of the drills that are necessary to master before you can get a nice clean backhand spring and move on to a more advance skill like a back tuck.
So keeping in mind all of those drills that I have shown you watch my backhand spring on this floor and see how everything I have done up to this moment leads me up to right here.
It is very important to be implemented into my technique using my backhand spring.
Watch how I jump off my toes last just like I did on the trampoline.
Watch how I extend my arms past my shoulders just like I did in the jump back and swing my arms quickly as I did in the arm string drill.
My sit is going to be very similar if not identical to the set that I did up against the wedge mat.
My arms are going to be nice and straight as they were in all the drills that I have showed you.
I?m going to block with my shoulders rather than bending my elbows like I did in all the blocking drills that I have showed you.
You are really going to be able to see how important it is to slow down, take the time to master each element of the backhand spring before tackling the backhand spring as a whole.
This is a backhand spring again on a floor.